

# **Marcos Campos**

🛚 Brasília, DF 📞 <u>61998750918</u> 🚇 <u>marcos.b.campos14@gmail.com</u>

https://github.com/marcos-c1

### Summary

I am a Bachelor's student in Computer Science at the Federal Institute of Brasília. I have professional experience acquired through academic and freelance competitions, as well as knowledge through improvements made throughout the academic journey. I'm passionate about programming and I need an opportunity in the job market to demonstrate my ability.

## **Professional Experience**

Public Ministry of the Federal District and Territories, Asa 09/2017 - 12/2017 Sul Asa Sul, Brasília

Estagiário

I worked in the Due Diligence department, my purpose was to update the procedural data in the system. Furthermore, he performed functions related to archiving cases and forwarding them to the appropriate courts.

Brazilian Hospital Services Company (EBSERH)

11/2020 - 04/2022

Estagiário

Asa Sul, DF

https://www.gov.br/ebserh/pt-br

I worked in the Personnel Analysis and Dimensioning Sector in the Data Science area, with the objective of providing efficient analytical tools based on the manipulation of data from the data warehouse.

## Federal Audit Court (TCU)

03/2022 - 03/2024

Estagiário

Asa Sul, DF

https://portal.tcu.gov.br/inicio/

I worked as a backend developer on TCU's Radex integrative system using pure JavaScript, the agile methodology applied in project management was SCRUM. The main objective of the Radex application was to provide users with an interactive interface around the deliberations of each process carried out in the control body's committees.

## **Caronas Burguer**

11/2023 - 01/2024

Freelancer

Tag. Norte, DF

https://www.caronasburger.com.br/

I worked as a frontend developer with the aim of making the application responsive, consistent and interactive with the user. The entire application is developed in pure PHP and the server is hosted by Apache.

#### Education

**Taguatinga Educational Center 05** 

02/2015 - 12/2017

Ensino Médio

Federal Institute of Brasília, Campus - Taguatinga

**02/2019 - Studying (last semester)**Ensino Superior

https://www.ifb.edu.br/taguatinga

**Skills** 

JavaScript, HTML, CSS

••••

**CRUD em APIs Restful**Protocolo HTTPS, SOAP

••••

Frameworks/Bibliotecas Back-End Express, Angular, JQuery

••••

Frameworks/Bibliotecas Front-End ReactJS, VueJS, NextJS, Redux, GraphQL

• • • • 0

Banco de Dados

MySQL, SQL Server, MongoDB, PostGreSQL, PL/SQL

••••

**Deploy da aplicação em Nuvem** Microsoft Azure, Amazon AWS

• • • • •

Ferramenta low-code

Oracle APEX, Power BI, Power Query

••••

Languages

C/C++/C#

••••

Java

••••

JavaScript

••••

**Typescript** 

Uso diariamente na criação de projetos freelancer

••••

**Python** 

Usei bastante python no meu Trabalho de Conclusão de Curso

••••

**PHP** 

• • • 0 0

Rust

••••

Go

••••

Lua

••••

Other languages

• • • • •